Mr. Sukhrob Ilyosbekov

Age: 21

Nationality: Uzbekistan

Email address: suxrobGM@gmail.com
Web: http://www.suxrobgm.net

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm LinkedIn: https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm

GitHub: https://github.com/suxrobGM



Profile

Thinking "out of the box" to provide software-based solutions

Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. Expert in C#, .NET, and T-SQL with database analysis and design. Skilled in developing business plans, requirements specifications, user documentation, and architectural systems research.

Software skills include:

- Languages: C#, C/C++, Java, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, XML, SQL
- Databases: MS SQL, PostgreSQL, Access, MySQL
- Software: Visual Studio, Rider, DataGrip, Visual Studio Code, DotPeek, Unity 3D
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Coding, testing and fixing programming errors.
- Collaborate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

Work experience

Pentalight Technology • Malaysia

Unity Developer

03/2020 - present

- Development multiplayer part of project.
- Integration User Interface
- Integration Photon Unity Networking
- Integration SteamVR

Freelancer.com

Freelance Software Developer

02/2019 – 02/2020

- Web Designing and Web Development.
- Worked closely with client to provide a customized website for their business.
- Design and development of various websites.
- Designing and maintaining front end for web and mobile applications.
- Writing unit tests to improve code predictability and documentation.
- Develop support tools to reduce working time from hours to minutes.
- Used coding methods in specific programming languages to initiate and improve program execution and functionality.

EC Dev Team • Uzbekistan

Game Developer

07/2016 – 02/2019

- Designing game Al logic
- Programming game mechanics
- Scripting game map
- Programming developers' tools
- Balancing game's difficulty.

Education

INTI International College Subang Subang Jaya • Malaysia

08/2019 - present

- American Degree Transfer Program
- Major: Computer Science

Tashkent University of Information Technologies Samarkand • Uzbekistan

09/2017 - 06/2019

- Bachelor of Science
- Major: Software Engineering

Awards

Top-10 team in IT Universities contest in Uzbekistan Tashkent University of Information Technologies

02/2018

• Top-10 team in contest between IT Universities in Uzbekistan

1st place in Individual ACM ICPC format contest Tashkent University of Information Technologies

12/2017

Winner in individual ACM ICPC format contest between TUIT students

Strengths

Ability to learn from mistakes • Creative thinking • Confident • Critical thinking • Working quickly • Accuracy • Solving complex problems

Skills

Programming Languages

C# *******

C/C++

Python ■■■■□

JavaScript ■■■□□

TypeScript ■■■■□

Java ■■■□□

PHP ■■□□□

HTML/CSS

SQL **BBBB**

Lua ■■□□□

Frameworks & Technologies

.NET ■■■■■

ASP.NET

WPF

Xamarin.Forms ■■■■□

ReactJS ■■■■□

Qt ■■□□

Unity 3D ■■■□

ML.NET

Entity Framework

Unit Testing ■■■□

Bootstrap 4

Git **EEEE**

ADO.NET ■■■□□

jQuery ■■■■

Publications

Introducing .NET 5

http://www.suxrobgm.net/Blog/Introducing-NET-5

05/2019

Introduction to Microsft's new technology .NET 5

ML.NET - Machine Learning for .NET

http://www.suxrobgm.net/Blog/Announcing-ML.NET

05/2019

At Finally! Microsoft announced ML.NET 1.0

Certificates

Certified Scrum Master - Agile Alliance

License 544689

2016

Open Source

Github - contributions in project Server Side Analytics https://github.com/matteofabbri/ServerSideAnalytics

Stackoverflow - https://stackoverflow.com/users/11926107/suxrobgm